dynamicsuser.net 2017-11-20

# Privacy policy - DUG

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribes to our newsletters, answer our surveys or becomes a user group member.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, city and country. As a member you're also asked optional to enter a your company name, job title, user type, birthday, gender, web address, blog, language, social media accounts and bio etc.. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Your DUG profile data is only fully visible to our members. Only name and other basic information are visible to everybody. But always consider what you share.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To process transactions 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering a request product or service.

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails 

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your membership, in addition to receiving occasional user group news, updates, related information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. Or by visiting your account settings.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Are DynamicsUser.net using cookies?

Yes. In fact we use several cookies when you use the different areas of our website.

### What are cookies?

Cookies are small files that a site or its service providers transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if your browser setup allows it) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

### What are you using the cookies for?

Cookies makes it easier to use the website, as we use the cookie to save information from visit to visit. We store information about your settings as well as your latest login, so that you don't have to enter it again. It also allows us to prevent that you see the same ads too many times. So it helps us improve our website and give our users a better experience when they visit our website. And I'm sure that we will use even more and more.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on DUG. Google's use of cookies enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### Is it possible to use the website without cookies?

Besides the fact that you would have to login every time you visit, then is also integrated into a lot of the functions on the website, so some parts will no longer work.

### How can I say no cookies from DUG?

You cannot. If you don't like them and don't know another way around using them, then please don't use our website. And forget about using any other international websites, as you most likely will not find any who doesn't use cookies.

### Why this cookie text?

Dynamics User Group is operating as a Danish registered company. And therefore we are required by both Danish and EU law to inform you about our use of cookies on our website.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://dynamicsuser.net/p/terms-of-use](https://dynamicsuser.net/p/terms-of-use).

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes (if major changes), and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on April 28 2016 (minor updates). 

### Contacting Us

If you have any concerns or questions about our privacy policy or information collected on our sites, please [contact webmaster Erik P. Ernst](https://dynamicsuser.net/contact.aspx) and he will reply promptly.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us

### Site Information

Dynamics User Group ApS  
Koervelvej 8  
5500 Middelfart  
Denmark  
webmaster@dynamicsuser.net  
http://dynamicsuser.net
